In the next part we're asked to create a DataFrame similar to the reviews
在下个部分 我们需要创建一个与 reviews 相似的DataFrame
but ranked by the rating for each user.
但是按照每位用户的评分排序
So basically, what we want to do in this part is to create a DataFrame where we sort
我们将创建一个 DataFrame
our values by the user ID first to keep all the user IDs together.
先按照 user_id 对值排序 将所有 user_id 放到一起
But then next we want to sort by the rating that they're given.
然后按照他们的评分排序
I'm just going to start this and ranked reviews.
将结果存储到 ranked_reviews 变量中
Okay. Then, I didn't read in the images but
Ok这个图片没有加载出来
if you're looking in the classroom or you're looking at the images yourself,
你可以在课堂里查看这个图片 也许你的图片会加载出来
basically what this is saying is if we take the dot product between two vectors
这个图片的含义是如果计算两个向量的点积
and we get something that's greater than zero,
并且结果大于 0
that gives us an indication that there's some overlap
那么这两个向量之间
between the two things that those vectors share.
有重叠的值
So, in terms of our content-based recommendations we
对于基于内容的推荐系统
can have a vector that look like this.
向量可以是这样的
If we take the dot product of this vector with itself and one of them its transpose,
如果计算这个向量与它本身的转置向量之间的点积
then what we would get is a two.
结果是 2
Basically what that means is that there were two things that were
表示这两项内容之间
shared between those two pieces of content.
有两部分是一样的
The larger that number the more pieces of information they share,
点积越大 它们共享的信息越多
and the smaller that number the less information they share.
点积越小 它们共享的信息越少
So, the nice part with this is that we can use the dot product to
所以 我们可以通过点积判断
then determine what movies are most alike other movies.
哪些电影与其他电影最相似
So, which movies are most similar.
即哪些电影最相似
Sorry, I shouldn't have called this movies.
抱歉 这里不应该称为 movies
Because I overwrote the movies DataFrame.
因为我覆盖了 movies DataFrame
So, the first thing
首先
I want to do is just pull the parts of the movies DataFrame
我将从 movies DataFrame 中
that are related to the content,
提取与内容有关的部分
which means we don't need the first three columns.
所以我们不需要前三列
So, I don't need the first three columns I only need the fourth column through will be
只需要从第四列一直到该 DataFrame 的最后一列
end of the DataFrame to be able to make content-based recommendations.
就能做出基于内容的推荐
Essentially, what we know from taking dot product is that if we take
通过点积运算我们知道
this matrix and we take the dot product of that matrix with itself transposed,
计算这个矩阵与它本身的转置矩阵的点积
then that should give us an idea,
将获得一个新的矩阵
it'll give us a new matrix that tells us which movies are most similar to one another.
这个矩阵会告诉我们哪些电影最相似
So, I'm just going this dot prod movies.
将这个称为 dot_prod_movies
We're going the.product dot product of this movies matrix with itself transposed,
我们将计算这个 movies 矩阵与它本身的转置矩阵之间的点积
and then that will give us this dot product movies
结果是这个 dot_prod_movies
which gives us some idea of which movies are most related to one another.
它可以告诉我们哪些电影相互关系最紧密
Where on the diagonal elements of this are going to be
对角线上的元素将值最大
the highest possible value which is the dot product of each movie with itself.
因为它们是每部电影与它本身的点积
So, that's the sum of the number of ones that are available in that movie row.
结果等于该电影行中存在的电影数量之和
So, this is probably going to take some time
可能需要运行一段时间
and then we can check our answer against the solution.
然后可以对照解答页面检查答案
If you correctly take the dot product of the content portions,
如果你正确地计算了内容部分的点积
you should get something that looks like this,
应该会看到这样一条消息
that says that you passed all the tests.
表示你通过了所有的测试